googletune.com 2018-08-18

# Information - privacy-policy

### Privacy Policy

* * *

**What information do we collect?**

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

We do not store or share usernames, profile pics or any other private information except user id & email (which is public). We take privacy very seriously. 

Our site relies on oAuth and you will never be encouraged or asked to share your password under any circumstances. You can de-authorize our application anytime by visiting Privacy section in your Facebook profile settings.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

; To send product updates

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**Do we use cookies?**

We do use cookies but over SSL only.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

http://googletune.com/  
admin@googletune.com
